<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All my writing</title>
    <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/_feed/story_feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>My writing, wow so cool</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Austere</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Austere/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The prime time is now! Want to surprise your loved ones with a gift that will CHANGE their lives for the holiday season? Buy the Austere Bot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Austere Bot will make everything in your easier, say goodbye to doing the laundry, dishes and MORE! The Austere Bot will do all these tasks for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you the type of person that prefers to do these things yourself but often forget to do so? Luckily for you the Austere Bot has a setting for that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just turn on the “Alarm” setting by flipping a switch on the Austere Bot and it will remind you to do your tasks! If you don&#39;t comply, the Austere Bot will start having your life feel chagrined!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will start doing the following actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closing your work calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deleting saved phone numbers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disallow outsiders into your house&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block all exits to the house&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiding your medication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All to make YOU focus on YOUR tasks easier!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what are you waiting for? Buy the Austere Bot now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;font-size:16px; margin:0px;&quot; class=&quot;bx2&quot;&gt;
By buying our product you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service. The company behind the Austere Bot, Stymphalia, will not be held liable for any damage caused by the product. Do not allow the product near young children or animals.
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Austere/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanahaki Ideas</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Hanahaki_Ideas/</link>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki that isn&#39;t based on love itself but can come from other emotions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of it originating from lack of interest in the other person, the hanahaki forces someone to actually confess, reciprocation of feelings isn&#39;t required to cure someone, hanahaki would be caused by the repression of emotions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essentially, hanahaki is just your body telling you: actually tell them how you feel, you idiot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki can come from many emotions: anger, love, hate etc... The flowers depend on the feelings, the amount varies depending on how intense the emotions are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asters for love, aconites for anger, among other things. Five flowers being coughed up are usually cured by vague posting online about the other person, ten flowers can be cured via indirect confession, but more than fifteen flowers have to be cured by directly confessing to the other. More flowers = more extreme the confession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flowers that represent worry are more common during times of plague, while love flowers would be more common during times of peace. Friendship flowers are the most common types of flowers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki can be dangerous but easily manageable so long as someone can afford the right medicine to avoid flare-ups, in more extreme cases the victim is either encouraged to go get surgery, which has the side effect of numbing any emotions for the other person, or to just confess&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a person dies, it&#39;s traditional for people to cough up grieving flowers and collect them to be used as decoration for the person&#39;s grave.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Hanahaki_Ideas/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermin</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Vermin/</link>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I burrow into your floors and I hide in your attic, I nibble and eat at the clothes you leave outside, I feed myself using the things you threw away. I am constantly on your mind. I weaken the foundation of your house. I writhe when you spray poison at me, you lived here long before I was born.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bite at your fingers when you try to hurt me. You slap me but feed me. You force me in clothes I can&#39;t stand to wear. The same clothes that I ate. I am vermin, that is what you think of people like me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don&#39;t know what I do, but we live in the same house. You tell me about the vermin outside, how they do bad things. I see myself in them. I see how they live when they are accepted by the other vermin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bite my fingers when ever you try to speak mean words about them. I itch my nose whenever you order pest control on them. I tell you that I&#39;m one of them, but you push me back into the floors and ignore what I told you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I dig my claws under my eyes. I tear off my claws with my teeth, and I hide in the attic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Vermin/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Prepare For A Hoard</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/How_to_Prepare_for_a_Hoard/</link>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;
   p{
    text-align: center;
   }

   h2{
    text-align: center;
   }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s important to remember that while your actions before the disaster are important, the preparations you make will be even more crucial to your survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Make sure the exterior is sturdy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check your house for any weak points, if there is a hole to the outside, cover it.
The infected are much more versatile than you think, and some people are infected with a strain that essentially liquefies their bones, which allows them to get through tight spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Set up your entry points&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure your doors are sturdy and check your windows for cracks. If your doors make a creaking sound, make sure to replace them. A creaking sound may attract an infected, and where there is one, there are usually more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Make sure to have a weapon nearby&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Self-explanatory, it&#39;s been five months since the infection has gotten out. If you aren&#39;t prepared to use a gun, then you aren&#39;t prepared to use self-defense when an infected is at your door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What if they get in?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the infected ever get in your home, it&#39;s not your fault. It really isn&#39;t. I am so sorry, please don&#39;t die, please don&#39;t. I am so lonely. The people I love are gone, they went out to get resources for me, I was so useless I am so sorry please forgive me please please please&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/How_to_Prepare_for_a_Hoard/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling Apart</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Falling_Apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I am falling apart, I miss the way you look at me. The way you smiled when I wasn&#39;t there to see. I feel sick when I see you, how you walk over the black dahlias that I grew for someone else, the way you read the books that I loved makes me feel like my organs have been torn off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ask you why you watch me at night and why you haunt me in mirrors that I broke. You laugh and brush off my questions. I asked why you planted dandelions in my garden, and you shrugged it off. I hate you. You planted weeds in my heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I see the way you gutted the sheep that I raised, they never wanted to be a part of this. Their soft white fleece, stained and hardened by the blood that you spilled on them. I heard their bleats of pain, but I couldn&#39;t help them. I was busy putting up the horseshoes that you left hanging upside down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You wanted a reaction out of me, but my reaction was in the presence of a blank face. You wanted me to scream and shout, but I couldn&#39;t. You saw the clothes that I was drying, and you burned them to try and help me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You made everything worse. You made me worse. You stare at me and beg for forgiveness, but that isn&#39;t what I wanted. I wanted to see you on your knees, I want you to sacrifice your heart and serve it to me on a platter. You say that you are sorry, but I know that you are lying.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.lexiqqq.com/creations/writing/Falling_Apart/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>